Everything fine? It's so soft (snow), pleasure (to ride) one more (guy) on otherside
すべて大丈夫ですか？とても柔らかいです （雪）、喜び（乗る） 反対側にもう1人（男）
everyone started from there? Is everything fine with you? I have not appropriate skies
みんなそこから始めたの？ すべて大丈夫ですか？ 私は適切な空を持っていません
I have joined fucking bullshit you don't have skies and don't have sticks
私はクソでたらめに参加しました あなたは空を持っていませんそして スティックを持っていません
one more person on that side, did you simply go down? yeah
その側にもう一人、 あなたはただ降りましたか？ うん
awesome then i turned to right to give you direction
驚くばかり それから私は右に曲がった あなたに方向性を与える
where's Markish? Markish on the top. riding slope
マーキッシュはどこ？ 上部にマークがあります。 ライディングスロープ
take a look at the guy sliding down on his ass, fuck, where? guys take a look at me
スライドする男を見てください 彼のお尻にダウン、ファック、どこ？ みんな私を見て
do you see where the trace from the skies? your path there between spruces
どこからのトレースがわかりますか 空？そこへのあなたの道 トウヒの間
don't go to the right because you need to go through that hill by feet
右に行かないでください あなたはそれを通過する必要があります 足で丘
(explaining the same)
（同じことを説明する）
that's the place where we need to gather ride here
それが私たちが必要とする場所です 集まる ここに乗る
it was scary a bit, but snow is like butter, you need wider skies
少し怖かったけど雪 バターのようなものです より広い空が必要です
let's go come to us (inaudible) i had the same on board
さあ行こう 私たちに来てください（聞こえない） 私は船上で同じものを持っていました
win, win, win, fuck everything else
勝つ、勝つ、勝つ、 他のすべてをファック
Thanks Mr. Roman for ride and skills
ローマさん、ありがとう 乗り心地とスキル
Skills are yours
スキルはあなたのものです
Are you going for another ride?
別の乗り物に行きますか？
I'm going
私は行きます
Snowboarder who was lost is going for another ride
迷子になったスノーボーダー 別の乗り物に行きます
I'm not going as I'm not able to ride such snow honestly
できないので行かない そんな雪に正直に乗る
Staying in touch
連絡を取り合う
It's funny
それはおかしいです
Sit near me
私の近くに座って
You're standing at the bottom and looking at the mountain, that's the right  and left side
あなたは一番下に立っています 山を見て、 それは右側と左側です
But we recognize sides the way we ride. Looking from top to bottom
しかし、私たちは側面を認識します 私たちの乗り方。見て 上から下まで
That's where our right and left Do you understand, yeah?
それが私たちの右と左の場所です 分かりますか
Because the way we look the way we ride
私たちの見た目が 私たちの乗り方
Now we are looking at the ski lift
今私たちは探しています スキーリフトで
That one
それです
During the ride we shall not cross that lift
乗車中、私たちは そのリフトを越えないでください
On the left that deep dive
左側にその深いダイビング
That deep dive called "couloir"
「クーロア」と呼ばれるその深いダイビング
Second navigation sign. Between us peak is located
2番目のナビゲーションサイン。 私たちの間にピークがあります
There is tree. We cross it by diagonal
木があります。私たちはそれを越えます 対角線で
From there, from that arm, the path is to the first valley
そこから、そこから 腕、道は 最初の谷
where the line of spruces are growing
ここでの行 トウヒは成長しています
no, you're simply riding. there is no hill to climb
いいえ、あなたはただ乗っているだけです。 登る丘はありません
second trail, where the sign from snowmobile in the middle, more narrow
2番目のトレイル。 スノーモービルからのサイン 途中で、 より狭い
there you pick the line to that forest, it's a gentle slope
そこにあなたはそれに線を選びます 森、なだらかな斜面
you can pass this track, or you can go through the forest and ski lift if you have good speed
このトラックを通過するか、 あなたは森を通り抜けることができます 良い場合はスキーリフト 速度
looking from here it's on the left, on that tongue, you can ride there boldly
ここから見ると 左、その舌の上、 大胆に乗れる
there if all four of us  will stay in one line, there will be enough space for all
私たち4人全員が 一列にとどまる、 すべての人に十分なスペースを確保する
snowcat can ride there and you are able, then going straight, in shadow snow is fine
雪上車はそこに乗ることができます そして、あなたはできる、そして行く まっすぐ、影の中で雪は大丈夫です
yeah, between forest and ski lift here to the bottom
ええ、森の間 ここにスキーリフトがあります ボトム
here you'll feel the snow will be clammy
ここであなたは雪を感じるでしょう ベトベトします
that snow may slide or may not The most important is not to ride ahead of the skies
その雪は滑るかもしれないかもしれない 最も重要なのは乗らないことです 空の前に
and going back here, if we are heading there
ここに戻って そこに向かって
that's rough plan
それは大まかな計画です
a bit higher than that ski lift
そのスキーリフトより少し高い
no need, we arrive, see the mountains from both sides and slide down here on the arm
必要ありません、私たちは到着します、 両側からの山 ここで腕を下にスライドさせます
it has a long horizontal cut, and from where you've started, you're simply riding, don't miss out
横に長いカットがあり、 そして、あなたが始めたところから、 あなたはただ乗っているだけです、 お見逃しなく
do not travere, you have good horizontal line
トラベリングしないでください、あなたは持っています 良い水平線
here the ski lift, here is another slope, don't go there
ここにスキーリフト、ここに 別の斜面、しないでください そこに行く
you can here, I think near ten people will fit
あなたはここでできると思います 10人近くが収まります
and from here how (to get to the centre)?
そしてここからどうやって （中心に行くために）？
so from here, we are going by the car (snowcat)? are you gonna get us?
だからここから行く 車で（雪上車）？ あなたは私たちを手に入れるつもりですか？
or we should take to the right? take to the right
または私たちは右に行く必要がありますか？ 右に曲がる
ok, then look
わかりました、それから見てください
or you can, fuck, go (inaudible), because we have a queue
またはあなたができる、ファック、行く（inaudible）、 キューがあるので
snowcat, slide down, four turns to the side yes
雪上車、下にスライド、 横に4回転 はい
and then i'm going to get you from here
そして、私は行きます ここからあなたを取得します
and then we'll take a look
それから見てみましょう
i'm gonna get you up to "skronya" and you 'll get bonus descend
私はあなたを取得するつもりです 「skronya」まで そして、あなたはボーナス下降を得るでしょう
clear. going down via snowcat is only when you don't have equipment or can't
クリア。雪上車で降りる あなたが持っていないときだけです 機器またはできない
clear. then car will going to get us from here
クリア。その後、車は行きます ここから私たちを取得するには
to have a logic of self slope riding, who wants where
自己の論理を持つこと スロープライディング、誰 どこに欲しい
Do you understand? Everything clear?
わかりますか？ すべてが明確ですか？
I've ride that slope by myself
あの坂に乗った 自分で
on the top will stay and take a look
上部にとどまります 見てください
and those who were riding slow, we'll wait for them to ride a bit
とだった人たち ゆっくり乗って、待ちます 彼らが少し乗るために
anyway, that 2 min wait, we'll reach them and outpace them
とにかく、その2分待つ、 私たちは彼らに到達し、 それらを上回ります
and will wait for them but we'll better look from there (the top)
そしてそれらを待ちます でも見た目は良くなります そこから（上）
to see where there are, we'll give 2-3 min handicap
どこにあるかを見るために、 2〜3分のハンディキャップを与えます
I don't see any company here maybe they jumped off
ここには会社がありません 多分彼らは飛び降りた
I went, and ski went sleek, but when that "cacao" started I feel skies are sticking
私が行って、スキーがなめらかになりました、 しかし、その「カカオ」が始まったとき 空がくっついている気がする
and I understand, when i make a turn, turning only me, not skies
そして私は理解します 曲がって、私だけを回して、 空ではない
like this, head and legs, and the only possibility is to give straight line
このように、頭と足、 そして唯一の可能性は 直線を与える
but guys, there are a couple of moments, when it's windy or when it's sunny
でもみんな、カップルがいます 風が強いときの瞬間 または晴れたとき
every hour, that's the other slope
毎時、それは 他の斜面
and if the sun will hide behind the mountain, and you'll go for thirds turn
そして太陽が隠れたら 山の後ろ、 そしてあなたは3分の1ターンに行きます
be ready to ride with a speed of a car
一緒に乗る準備をしてください 車の速度
"pedal to floor" so called slope is frozen and no control
いわゆる「床へのペダル」 斜面が凍っている 制御なし
speed will be incredible, the slope will be like a glass Of course
スピードは信じられないほどになります、 斜面はガラスのようになります もちろん
Roman let me write your phone number of course, what's your name?
ローマ人は私にあなたを書かせてくれます 電話番号 もちろん、あなたの名前は何ですか？
Bohdan Hi Bohdan, my passed away brother was named Bohdan
ボーダン こんにちはボーダン、亡くなりました 兄はボーダンと名付けられました
(telling number)
（電話番号）
Why Oaza (ski loft)  doesn't work? It's all resulted to the fact
オアザ（スキーロフト）がしない理由 仕事？それはすべて結果です 事実に
that there are not a lot of people, plus quarantine, transport doesn't work
あまりないこと 人々、および検疫、 輸送が機能しない
I think for the owner it was not profitable for 2-3 people make busy a lot of personnel
オーナーにとってはそうだったと思います 2〜3人は儲からない 多くの人員を忙しくさせる
work for regional electric provide. one engine here consumes 100 kWh on a ski lift
地域の電気のために働く 提供。ここに1つのエンジン スキーリフトで100kWhを消費します
plus to start all of these plus feed all of them and you understand that every day
さらに、これらすべてを開始します プラスそれらすべてを養い、 あなたは毎日それを理解しています
if you don't have profit, you consume profit from winter
あなたが利益を持っていない場合、あなたは 冬からの利益を消費する
we had the same situation on the central slope on Drahobrat, Kuryatnya
同じ状況でした 中央斜面 Drahobrat、Kuryatnyaに
the personnel went out, only locals left in pulse mode On Kuryatnya, Vasya is
職員が出て行っただけ 地元の人々はパルスモードのままです Kuryatnyaでは、Vasyaは
doing two jobs simultaneously, operating ski lift and selling ski passes
2つの仕事を同時に行う、 スキーリフトの操作と販売 スキーパス
rental guy also dispatcher for instructors, we work through the school
レンタル男もディスパッチャー インストラクターのために、私たちは働きます 学校を通して
people came, took equipment, paid out to the dispatcher, at the appointer time
人々が来て、機器を取り、 コーディネーターに支払い、 アポインター時に
the instructor arrived, person worked, you feel safe, plus you can schedule a day
インストラクターが到着しました、人 働いた、あなたは安全だと感じます、 さらに、1日をスケジュールすることができます
you are going somewhere, sleeping...
あなたはどこかに行きます、 睡眠...
*looking on Maps for direction*
*地図で方向性を探しています*
Ehehey, i'm heading to Oaza
Ehehey、私はオアザに向かっています
you have specified time, you have to whom talk to
あなたは時間を指定しました、 あなたは誰と話をする必要があります
on the phone, where that instructor disappeared
電話で、それは インストラクターが姿を消した
and he may have already planned his personal life and enjoying
そして彼はすでに持っているかもしれません 彼の個人的な生活を計画しました 楽しんで
on the instruction of winter *inaudible*, who has snot, that one on the bottom
冬の指導について 鼻水を持っている* inaudible *、 一番下にあるもの
the one who has what? the one who has snot is on the bottom
何を持っている人？ 鼻水を持っている人 底にあります
what if both have snot? snot? yes
両方に鼻が付いている場合はどうなりますか？ 鼻水？ はい
there is always something like I'm on the right, you're on the right, I'm on top, you're on top
いつものようなものがあります 私は右側にいます、あなたは 右、私は上にいる、あなたは上にいる
we won't be able to walk to "Kuryatnya" from here?
歩けなくなります ここから「Kuryatnya」へ？
let's see, are you going for another ride? I'm simply asking what to do
見てみましょう、行きますか 別の乗り物のために？ 私は単に何をすべきかを尋ねています
no, are you going one more time? for one more descend
いいえ、もう一度行きますか？ もう1つ降りる
i'm thinking, if i can reach "Kuryatnya" from here
届くかと思って ここから「Kuryatnya」
but we are not going to "Kuryatnya", we gather here and move to slope peak
しかし、私たちは行きません 「Kuryatnya」、ここに集まる スロープピークに移動します
like i'm showing via my hand
手で見せているように
and going back here, riding slope down to the car
ここに戻って、 車に向かって坂を下る
there is no other way, only if you want...
他に方法はありません、 必要な場合のみ...
I'm asking if "Kuryatnya" is long away from here
「Kuryatnya」は ここから遠く離れて
right after "Psyachiy" pass
「Psyachiy」パス直後
about 200 meters you'll need to go by feet uphill
約200メートル 上り坂を足で行く必要があります
on top, there is a station, that kennel, do you see it?
上に駅があり、 あの犬小屋、見えますか？
after reaching it going down and moving right
それに到達した後 下に移動して右に移動
200 meters and you're on "Chayka"
200メートルと あなたは「チャイカ」にいます
Everything is fine? Yes
すべて順調？ はい
Whose snowboard wants to move the slope? Don't leave it
誰のスノーボード 斜面を動かしたいですか？ 放置しないでください
Last year, Vitaliy Kopeyking is saying,
昨年、Vitaliy Kopeykingは言っています、
the woman comes which took snowboard for rent
女性が来る スノーボードを借りた
and saying that snowboard fell on the other side of the hill
スノーボードが落ちたと言って 丘の向こう側
and that she'll give 1000 UAH for that snowboard to return
そして彼女は1000UAHを与えるでしょう そのスノーボードが戻るために
I and Eugene thought why not? Used ski lift, descended down the hill about 100 meters
私とユージーンはどうしてだろうと思いましたか？ 使用済みスキーリフト、下降 丘を下って約100メートル
Stayed and saw snowboard starring from the ground Hooray, we found it
滞在してスノーボードを見た 地面から主演 やったー、見つけた
Tightened it to the bag, looking on the bottom, from the snow only some colors seen
見て、バッグに締めました 底に、雪から 一部の色のみが表示されます
and that's another snowboard who was lost at the beginning of the winter
それは別のスノーボードです 最初に迷子になった人 冬の
Snowboard, once it's lost and jumping to the bottom of the hill can drop on binding
スノーボード、紛失したら 一番下にジャンプします 丘の
or protrude from the snow, like a rocket
または雪から突き出て、 ロケットのように
grabing second snowboard, i've tightened to my bag, once we at Vitalik's place
2番目のスノーボードをつかむ、 鞄を締めて、 ヴィタリックの家に着いたら
He looks at boards and saying that's not the lost one, but I'm buying immediately
彼はボードを見て言っています それは失われたものではありませんが、私は すぐに購入
In 45 minutes we sold 2 snowboards, and going for the third one
45分で販売しました スノーボード2枚、 3番目のもののために
Ski lift worker is telling, guys ascended the hill, stayed to make a photo
スキーリフトの労働者は言っています、 男たちは丘を登った、 写真を撮るために滞在しました
4 snowboards put againsts ski lift, gust of wind, 4 boards like domino fell
対抗する4つのスノーボード スキーリフト、突風、4枚のボード ドミノが落ちたように
4 boards one after another, like ducks one after another
次々と4枚のボード、 次々とアヒルのように
I'm going to tell you, my friend, once you descended somewhere and don't know the route
私はあなたに言うつもりです、私の友人、 どこかに降りたら ルートがわからない
and you don't have snowshoes neither sticks and your board costs like Jeep from Poland
スノーシューはありません スティックもボードも ポーランドのジープのような費用
so, somewhere at the 10th kilometer of your wandering, it costs zero and you're throwing it away
だから、10キロのどこかで あなたの放浪の、それはゼロの費用がかかります そしてあなたはそれを捨てています
because you understand that you cannot carry it
あなたがそれを理解しているので あなたはそれを運ぶことはできません
you're going 20 meters in such snow for an hour
あなたは20メートル行く そのような雪の中で1時間
Did you start from "Jandarm" with me or with another Roman? I slid down with you
「ジャンダルム」から始めましたか 私と、または別のローマ人と？ 私はあなたと一緒に滑り落ちました
Somewhere near half of the slope So tell me, please,  why did you go there where you shouldn't?
斜面の半分近くのどこか 教えてください、なぜあなたは 行ってはいけないところに行きますか？
I'm in shock, I was thinking just for a moment, I went off the route
私はショックを受けています、私は考えていました ちょっとの間、私は行きました ルート外
I knew that I need to turn left but why are you not doing this? I turned not enough
私は左に曲がる必要があることを知っていました しかし、なぜあなたはこれをしないのですか？ 私は十分に向きを変えませんでした
I have even seen a red sign more than asking I wouldn't do more for you
赤い看板も見たことがあります 尋ねる以上に あなたのためにもっとやる
you don't need to behave like that, I was simply sliding down here for the first time
あなたはのように振る舞う必要はありません それは、私は単に滑り降りていた ここで初めて
you've been shown points of direction, go to the first then to another
あなたはポイントを見せられました 方向の、​​最初に行きます その後、別の
sorry, i've relaxed just for a few seconds, okay
すみません、私はただリラックスしました 数秒、大丈夫
because you're alone and no one knows which direction you selected
あなたが一人だから 誰も知らない 選択した方向
if something happens to you, unlikely someone will help you yeah, understand this dangerous
あなたに何かが起こったら、 誰かがあなたを助ける可能性は低い ええ、この危険を理解してください
I've simply gone too much forward I knew I need to turn left but turned too late, sorry
私は単に前進しすぎた 左に曲がる必要があることはわかっていましたが 手遅れになりました、ごめんなさい
are we going for another ride? dude, I didn't enjoy it, first of all I'm complete null in this
私たちは別の乗り物に行きますか？ おい、私はそれを楽しんでいませんでした、最初に 私はこれで完全にnullです
second, wet snow, I'm not prepared for that, I would go for a couple of times
第二に、湿った雪、私は違います そのための準備をして、私は行きます 数回
we'll see and decide guys, one moment, the way we discussed, don't invent a bicycle
私たちは見て決定します みんな、一瞬、私たちのやり方 話し合って、自転車を発明しないでください
one more turn, one more hill, I'll find a way, no you won't the mountain won't let you out
もう一回転、もう一丘、 私は方法を見つけます、あなたはしません 山はあなたを解放しません
there is a reason why the route is being preselected, indicators of direction, I see spruce
ルートが理由があります 事前に選択されている、インジケーター 方向の、​​私はトウヒを見る
you see an apple tree, we discuss indicators which we don't pass through or by which we turn
あなたはリンゴの木を見ます、私たちは話し合います 合格しない指標 を介して、またはそれによって私たちは向きを変えます
I didn't know you were here I asked if there was anybody there? someone replied yes, one went
あなたがここにいるとは知りませんでした 誰かいるの？ 誰かがそう答えた、1つは行った
if you want to change the route, all should be aware and prediscussed
ルートを変更したい場合は、 すべてが認識している必要があります 事前に議論された
but no one is blaming simply don't do like that if we agreed on a route, we go
しかし、誰も非難していません 単にそのようにしないでください ルートに合意したら、
(inaudible)
（聞き取れない）
So what? Let's go away? I would ride one more time I can not ride this wet snow
だから何？立ち去ろうか？ もう一度乗る この濡れた雪には乗れない
are you going to ride on Kuryatnya? yes
乗るつもりですか Kuryatnya？はい
on the left, there is a couloir, we don't go there, on the right ski lift, in front of the slope
左側にクーロアがあり、 そこには行かない、右側 ゲレンデ前のスキーリフト
straight from the top shelf, here near the forest, but not from the peak
一番上の棚からまっすぐ、 ここ森の近く、 ピークからではありません
I've started recording
録音を始めました
We are going to ride fucking there to that ski lift
乗る そこにクソ スキーリフト
Now we are looking at the ski lift
今、私たちはスキーリフトを見ています
I've almost fucked up
私はほとんどめちゃくちゃになりました
Mr. Bohdan can't catch up with us
ボーダンさんはできません 私たちに追いつく
Great (ride)
グレート（ライド）